y-axis.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy - Y-Axis

Y-Axis Overseas Careers recognizes the importance of preserving complete confidentiality. Any personal information and/or business proprietary material that you might disclose to us is treated with strict confidence.

All information given to Y-Axis by its prospective clients is kept strictly confidential and on a need-to-know basis and is protected. We will only record your personal details if you send us a message. You can be assured that your personal information is used only by our trained staff for the purpose of the work you have engaged our office to do.

We will not use your e-mail address for any other purpose, and will not disclose it, without your consent. Your information is never used for marketing or solicitation and is never sold or given to anyone for these purposes.

Y-Axis Overseas Careers never supplies any other person or organization with your information except those government agencies involved in your immigration process (e.g. Australian Immigration Authorities, DIAC or the Home Office, UK, etc.).

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter, catalog or updates on our new products and services. The information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you have given us your specific consent to do so.

The website has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We encrypt all of your personal and financial information and use our best efforts to prevent it from being read or intercepted as the information travels over the Internet. While we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

The Site provides links to websites and access to content, products and services from third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. You agree that Y-Axis is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on, third party websites. The User is requested to peruse the policies posted by other websites regarding privacy and other topics before use. Y-Axis is not responsible for third party content accessible through the Site, including opinions, advice, statements and advertisements, and User shall bear all risks associated with the use of such content. Y-Axis is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort User may incur from dealing with any third party.

Our Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions may change from time to time. Clients should check our website frequently to see any recent changes. Our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account, unless stated otherwise.

For further details, please [ **Talk to an expert**](http://web.igenero.in/contactus/) ** ** or you can e-mail us on [ **info@y-axis.com**](mailto:info@y-axis.com). One of our representatives will get back to you at the earliest.

We are License Recruitment Agent in India(B-0553/AP/COM/1000+/5/8968/2013)
